Xiao Yi
샤오이
This is the woman who lives next door to him
이 사람은 그 옆집에 사는 여자야.
suspects
용의자
from now on
지금부터
in this case
이 경우
The woman who lives next door to him
그 옆집에 사는 여자
perhaps
아마도
we have been looking for
우리는 찾고 있었어요
This is Mr. Zhang
장씨입니다
Xiao Yi's photos
샤오이의 사진
we got it
우리는 그것을 얻었다
But be careful with this woman
하지만 이 여자를 조심하세요
very high
매우 높다
We went to their neighborhood
우리는 그들의 동네에 갔다
But the surveillance camera was found
그런데 감시 카메라가 발견됐어요
they were cheated
그들은 속았다
So we didn't find
그래서 우리는 못 찾았어
any direct photos
직접 찍은 사진
Where is the inspection team?
검사팀은 어디에 있나요?
they entered her house
그들은 그녀의 집에 들어갔다
Verify
확인하다
I hope in the future
앞으로도 바랍니다
Find other evidence
다른 증거 찾기
under any circumstances
어떤 경우 에라도
Master Zhang finally appeared
드디어 장 선생님이 등장했습니다
How is Chu Yan?
추얀은 어때요?
Yes
예
She knows it's limited
그녀는 그것이 제한되어 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다
you didn't go
당신은 가지 않았다
In Xiao Yi’s life
샤오이의 삶에서
Let me see the interrogation video
심문 영상을 보시죠
except name
이름 빼고
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
Other information about him
그에 대한 다른 정보
For example
예를 들어
another phone number
다른 전화번호
family address
가족 주소
or
또는
Do you have any friends in common?
공통점이 있는 친구가 있나요?
No
아니요
these glasses
이 안경
When did you buy it?
언제 구입하셨나요?
This is from Xiaoyi
이건 샤오이에서 온 거야
when
언제
a week ago
일주일 전
I was very busy
나는 매우 바빴다
Ignore him for now
지금은 그를 무시하세요
but he remembers
하지만 그 사람은 기억해
our memory
우리의 기억
All right
괜찮은
What crime did he commit?
그는 어떤 범죄를 저질렀나요?
Don't worry about him now
이제 그 사람 걱정하지 마세요
but you
하지만 당신은
did you see?
봤어?
You are doing it for him now
당신은 지금 그를 위해 그것을하고 있습니다
you have not
너는 ..하지 않았다
no usable value
사용할 수 있는 값이 없습니다
Is everything fake?
모든 것이 가짜인가요?
Maybe even his name
어쩌면 그의 이름조차
Forged
서서히 나아가는
But you helped him
하지만 당신이 그 사람을 도와줬어요
Steal state secrets
국가기밀을 훔치다
this is correct
이게 맞다
on the way back
돌아 오는 길에
What did he tell you?
그가 당신에게 무엇을 말했습니까?
He said he would take me to see the sunrise
그는 나를 일출을 보러 데려가겠다고 하더군요
sunrise
해돋이
Yes
예
Because I'm always dreaming
왜냐면 난 항상 꿈을 꾸고 있으니까
Want to own a villa by the sea
바다 옆에 별장을 갖고 싶다
I can watch the sunrise
일출을 볼 수 있어요
Go watch the sunrise and sunset
일출과 일몰을 보러 가세요
Can you wear these glasses?
이 안경을 써도 되나요?
one
하나
beach villa
비치 빌라
Do you think Xiao Yi will accept it?
샤오이가 받아들일 것 같나요?
before saying this
이 말을 하기 전에
He didn't know he had been exposed
그는 자신이 노출된 것을 몰랐다
but he
그러나 그는
Do whatever it takes to please
기쁘게 하기 위해 필요한 것은 무엇이든 하세요
Chu Yan’s wish
추옌의 소원
Tianyang, what do you think?
텐양 씨, 어떻게 생각하세요?
Given their event rules
이벤트 규칙을 고려하면
He won't buy a villa
그 사람은 빌라를 사지 않을 거예요
But it can be rented
하지만 렌탈은 가능해요
let us check
확인해 보자
OK
좋아요
I'll ask the technical department
기술부서에 물어볼게요
Verify
확인하다
Xiaoyi’s consumption record
Xiaoyi의 소비 기록
Probably
아마
a hiding place
은신처
welcome
환영
The number you dialed is out of service
당신이 거신 번호는 서비스가 종료된 번호입니다
I found Xiao Yi’s residence
샤오이의 집을 찾았어요
three days ago
3 일전
Sea view villa for rent
바다 전망 빌라 임대
a month
한 달
Have you informed Director Chen?
첸 국장에게 알렸나요?
Yes
예
Other groups have taken off
다른 그룹은 떠났어요
Go to website
웹사이트로 이동
Okay, I'll go right away
알았어, 바로 갈게
are you looking for me?
나를 찾고 있나요?
waiting for me
나를 기다려 줘
I let go
나는 놓아주었다
Shall we go together?
같이 갈래?
I take a gun with me in the shower
나는 샤워할 때 총을 가지고 다닌다
And you can't take a shower with a gun
그리고 총을 들고 샤워를 할 수는 없습니다
kill me
나를 죽여라
impossible
불가능한
mission accomplished
임무 완수
I'll brush my teeth first
먼저 이를 닦을게요
Didn’t we agree to clean up first?
우리가 먼저 청소하기로 동의하지 않았나요?
The same to you
너도 마찬가지야
Have you gained weight recently?
최근에 살이 쪘나요?
you must kill him
너는 그를 죽여야 해
you know a lot
당신은 많은 것을 알고 있습니다
besides it
게다가
.Full Revealed
.전체 공개
They are afraid that you will not be able to escape from Tianhai.
그들은 당신이 천해에서 탈출하지 못할까 봐 두려워합니다.
if i say
내가 말하면
I can find a way to go
나는 갈 길을 찾을 수 있어요
I can't kill you
나는 당신을 죽일 수 없습니다
I didn't complete the task
작업을 완료하지 못했습니다.
I'm not here to kill you
난 널 죽이러 온 게 아니야
You betrayed the organization
넌 조직을 배신했어
you know i have no choice
나한테 선택의 여지가 없다는 거 알잖아
now my work is done
이제 내 일은 끝났어
I can't kill you
나는 당신을 죽일 수 없습니다
you have completed your task
당신은 당신의 임무를 완료했습니다
Your skink is poisonous
너의 스킹크는 유독하다
follow me
나를 따라와
are you happy?
행복하니?
I'm your partner
나는 당신의 파트너입니다
very good
매우 좋은
Xiao Yi was poisoned
샤오이가 독살당했어요
Quickly
빠르게
Call an ambulance quickly
빨리 구급차를 불러주세요
science
과학
Come on, be careful
자, 조심하세요
come over
이리와
Sorry, you can't enter
죄송합니다. 입장하실 수 없습니다
He went to the emergency room
그는 응급실에 갔다
Has it been processed?
처리됐나요?
Yes
예
But Guoan came quickly
하지만 궈안은 빨리 왔어요
no time to be sure
확신할 시간 없어
this matter
이 문제
cannot have any errors
오류가 있어서는 안 된다
you killed him
당신이 그를 죽였어
if he is still alive
만약 그가 아직 살아있다면
Will he help us?
그 사람이 우리를 도와줄까?
To keep a secret?
비밀을 지키려고?
Is he alive or dead?
그는 살아있나요, 죽었나요?
Give me an explanation
설명 좀 해주세요
Understood
이해했다
Sister, you're late
언니, 늦었어요
Good morning, President
좋은 아침입니다, 대통령님
Good morning, Sir
좋은 아침입니다, 선생님
Sister, I'm done
언니, 이제 끝났어요
Are you OK
괜찮으세요
I am fine
괜찮아요
Go to work
일하러 가다
OK
좋아요
How is the patient?
환자는 어떻습니까?
Although temporarily saved
일시적으로 저장되었지만
but his signs of life
하지만 그의 삶의 흔적
unstable
불안정한
at any time
언제든지
72 hours later
72시간 후
Very important
매우 중요
We have to continue to monitor
계속해서 모니터링을 해야 합니다
How long will it take
얼마나 걸릴까요
Handshake
악수
if he could
만약 그가 할 수 있었다면
he can succeed
그는 성공할 수 있다
I think it's very likely
내 생각엔 그럴 가능성이 매우 높아
he will get up early
그 사람 일찍 일어날 거야
he told the police
그는 경찰에게 말했다
It turns out that this villa
알고 보니 이 빌라는
Because it is rented out
임대로 운영되기 때문에
there are many people there
거기 사람이 많아
Therefore, it is very difficult to investigate
따라서 조사가 매우 어렵습니다.
As for the examination group
심사그룹의 경우
Only in this villa
이 빌라에만 있어요
in this villa
이 빌라에서
about 37
약 37
Judging from female footprints
여자 발자국으로 판단
It's for Mr. Zhang
장 씨를 위한 거예요
do something
뭔가를 해라
Help yourself
알아서 드세요
The inspection team found
검사팀이 발견한
Other fingerprints are incomplete
다른 지문은 불완전합니다.
not long ago
요전
when i enter the villa
내가 빌라에 들어갈 때
Judging from the clarity of this fingerprint
이 지문의 선명함으로 판단하면
we can judge
우리는 판단할 수 있다
he recently left her
그는 최근에 그녀를 떠났다
Only half a piece
반 조각만
But honestly
하지만 솔직히
This fingerprint
이 지문
doesn't make much sense to us
우리에겐 별로 의미가 없어
we don't know at all
우리는 전혀 모른다
Where is the owner of the fingerprint?
지문의 주인은 어디에 있나요?
Do you have any opinion
당신은 어떤 의견이 있습니까?
OK
좋아요
eat
먹다
my sisters
내 자매들
I gotta go
난 가야 해
See you tomorrow
내일 봐요
sorry i came too late
미안 내가 너무 늦게 왔어
I see you're activating night flight mode
야간 비행 모드를 활성화하고 계시군요
I know you are busy again
너 또 바쁜 거 알아
Yes
예
Cook a pot of pasta
파스타 한 냄비 요리하기
OK
좋아요
I want to drink some wine
와인 좀 마시고 싶어
a cup of beer
맥주 한 잔
Pasta with beer
맥주와 파스타
Fashion
패션
Would you like a drink too?
너도 한잔 할래?
OK
좋아요
comfortable
편안한
can you help me
도와주세요
Some dishes with wine
와인과 함께하는 몇 가지 요리
no problem
괜찮아요
Thanks
감사해요
eat slowly
천천히 먹어
I'm hungry
배고파요
let's go
갑시다
Thanks
감사해요
Are you OK
괜찮으세요
Can't compare
비교할 수 없다
We only have half of our fingerprints
우리는 지문의 절반만 갖고 있다
your mark
당신의 표시
Fingerprints are not clear
지문이 선명하지 않음
unconfirmed
확인되지 않은
The boundaries have been blurred
경계가 흐릿해졌어
look
바라보다
these places
이 장소들
Remove skin from fingers
손가락에서 피부를 제거하십시오.
Will it cause fingerprint haze?
지문이 흐려질까요?
Yes
예
Xiao Yi is still alive
샤오이는 아직 살아있습니다
He may wake up at any time
그 사람은 언제든지 깨어날 수 있어요
How are you going to deal with Huang Ziqing?
황자칭을 어떻게 상대할 건가요?
Since Huang Ziqing
황자경 이후
He is Gao Tianyang's informant
그는 Gao Tianyang의 정보원입니다
for us
우리를 위해
worthless
가치 없는
He will not return to Tianhai alive
그는 살아서 천해로 돌아오지 못할 것이다
Huang Zicheng was killed
황자성(黃紫成)이 살해당했다
means nothing to you
너에겐 아무 의미도 없어
Of course it has its meaning
물론 그 의미도 있어요
He will make these
그는 이것들을 만들 것이다
who wants to deceive us
누가 우리를 속이려고 하는가
Don't you dare lie anymore?
이제 더 이상 거짓말을 할 수 없나요?
if you want to kill him
그를 죽이고 싶다면
No need to wait long
오래 기다릴 필요가 없습니다
Still very useful
여전히 매우 유용합니다
yaw yaw
요 요
You are becoming more and more like me
넌 점점 나와 닮아가고 있어
experienced spy
경험이 풍부한 스파이
No wonder Mr. Yu
당연하지 유 씨
I don't want to abandon you
나는 당신을 버리고 싶지 않아요
Huang Ziqing is definitely helpful
황자경(Huang Ziqing)은 확실히 도움이 됩니다
But this mission
하지만 이번 미션은
you need to finish it
너는 그것을 끝내야 해
What is the mission?
임무는 무엇입니까?
Search for "Gao Tianyang".
"가오텐양"을 검색하세요.
Looking for Gao Tianyang
가오텐양을 찾아서
open the door
문을 열어라
let's eat
먹자
go out to eat
먹으러 가자
my sisters
내 자매들
Can I come up for air?
바람쐬러 올라와도 될까요?
No
아니요
allow
허용하다
Okay, okay, can I go?
알았어 알았어 가도 돼?
go see tony
토니를 만나러 가세요
No
아니요
my sister my sister
내 여동생 내 여동생
no problem, no problem
문제 없어, 문제 없어
Eat food
음식을 먹고
presentable
표현 가능한
we need to
우리는해야
Better than Huang Zicheng
황자성보다 낫다
You want to exploit Huang Ziqing?
Huang Ziqing을 이용하고 싶습니까?
To bring out the sunset
일몰을 꺼내기 위해
It's Gao Tianyang
가오텐양이에요
in our plan
우리 계획에
But we must start early
하지만 우리는 일찍 시작해야 해요
But this is from Duane
하지만 이건 Duane이 보낸 거야
He wants to pull it out
그 사람은 그걸 꺼내고 싶어해
What will happen?
무슨 일이 일어날 것?
it depends
때에 따라 다르지
for him
그를 위해
everything
모든 것
You need to analyze the pros and cons
장단점을 분석해야합니다
It’s just that the chip doesn’t fit
칩이 안맞아서 그런거임
No transaction is possible
거래가 불가능합니다
Why do you want me to leave?
왜 내가 떠나길 바라나요?
If Gao Tianyang disagrees
Gao Tianyang이 동의하지 않는 경우
I will fall into a trap
함정에 빠지겠다
You are Huang Ziqing’s partner
당신은 황자칭의 파트너입니다
I've met Gao Tianyang before
나는 전에 Gao Tianyang을 만난 적이 있어요
No one is more suitable for you
당신에게 더 적합한 사람은 없습니다
Can Huang Zicheng come back alive?
황자성(Huang Zicheng)은 살아날 수 있을까?
depends on you
너에게 달렸다
Do you think
당신은 생각합니까?
Can I deal with Gao Tianyang?
Gao Tianyang과 거래할 수 있나요?
No need to pay attention to him
그 사람한테 신경 쓸 필요 없어
Just let him know
그 사람한테만 알려줘
it's dangerous
이건 위험 해
As for other arrangements
그밖의 정리로는
I will tell you
난 당신을 말할 것이다
we will understand the situation
우리는 상황을 이해할 것입니다
and are always available to help you
항상 도움을 드릴 수 있습니다
Hello
안녕하세요
My brother Tianyang
내 동생 천양
This is me Yaoyao
나 야오야오야
What happened to Huang Ziqing?
황자칭에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Take him out of the night fog
밤안개 속에서 그를 데리고 나가
Where is he now?
그는 지금 어디에 있나요?
in the same boat
같은 배에서
Why did they arrest him?
그들은 왜 그를 체포했나요?
Because Huang Zicheng is your informant
Huang Zicheng은 귀하의 정보원이기 때문에
Who said that?
누가 말했다?
He said so himself
그 자신도 그렇게 말했다
Huang Ziqing and I
황자칭과 나
I'm the pawn in your quarrel
나는 네 싸움의 전당포야
listen carefully
잘 들어
you can sit here now
이제 여기 앉아도 돼
she talks to me
그녀는 나에게 말을 걸어요
I hid
나는 숨었다
For you
당신을 위한
Otherwise you will arrest him
그렇지 않으면 그를 체포할 것이다
this is my man
이 사람은 내 남자야
To present you with results
결과를 여러분께 선보이기 위해
Did you cheat on him?
그 사람을 속였나요?
I'm asking you
나는 당신에게 묻는다
How did they know?
그들은 어떻게 알았습니까?
find out
알아내다
The documents Huang Ziqing took were fake
황자칭이 가져간 문서는 가짜였다
He forced me to investigate him
그는 나에게 그를 조사하라고 강요했다
I know
알아요
sorry
죄송합니다
I have no expectations
나는 기대가 없다
it's important
그것은 중요하다
therefore
그러므로
I didn't expect anything
나는 아무것도 기대하지 않았다
at the beginning
처음에
you play games together
너는 같이 게임을 해
Why don't you think about it?
그것에 대해 생각해 보는 게 어때?
What's the end of today?
오늘의 끝은 무엇입니까?
but me too
하지만 나도 마찬가지야
force me
저를 강제로
to this limit
이 한도까지
Do you think you are innocent?
당신은 결백하다고 생각하십니까?
I'm not innocent
나는 결백하지 않다
i know i did it
나도 내가 그랬다는 걸 알아
many errors
많은 오류
He doesn't deserve to forgive me
그 사람은 나를 용서할 자격이 없어
but i still want to
하지만 난 아직도 그러고 싶어
To Huang Zicheng
황쯔쳉에게
to find you
너를 찾기 위해
i want to tell you
나는 당신에게 말하고 싶다
everything
모든 것
you can
당신은 할 수
at any time
언제든지
But my brother Tianyang
하지만 내 동생 텐양(Tianyang)
please
제발
Please save Huang Ziqing
황자칭을 구해주세요
Because you are the only one now
지금은 너뿐이니까
to save him
그를 구하기 위해
What are their conditions?
그들의 조건은 무엇입니까?
Tony said
토니가 말했다.
He wants to see you alone
그 사람은 당신을 혼자 보고 싶어해요
you can go alone
혼자 가도 돼
Where?
어디?
Mr. Gao Tianyang
가오텐양 씨
welcome
환영
Don't you want to meet and talk?
만나서 이야기하고 싶지 않으세요?
This is also an interview
이것도 인터뷰다
in this era
이 시대에
distance is not a problem
거리는 문제가 되지 않는다
Where is Huang Zicheng?
황쯔청은 어디에 있나요?
He's here
그는 여기에 있습니다
let me see
좀 보자
we haven't talked yet
우리 아직 얘기 안 했는데
before we talk
우리 얘기하기 전에
Not very good
아주 좋은하지
hurry up
서둘러요
Huang Ziqing was released
황자경(黃子淸)이 석방되다
what is it
그게 뭐야?
Get rid of Xiao Yi
샤오이를 없애라
Do you think it's possible?
가능하다고 생각하시나요?
She wants me to kill someone
그 사람은 내가 누군가를 죽였으면 좋겠어
Persons protected by the National Security Agency
국가안전보위부의 보호를 받는 사람
i don't care what i do
난 내가 뭘 하든 상관 안 해
we just want results
우리는 단지 결과를 원할 뿐
i can't do this
난 이걸 할 수 없어
presentable
표현 가능한
I'll give you some time to think
생각할 시간을 좀 드릴께요
Xiao Yi and Huang Zicheng
샤오이(Xiao Yi)와 황쯔쳉(Huang Zicheng)
Who is most important?
누가 가장 중요한가?
Did you cheat on him?
그 사람을 속였나요?
but I do not have
하지만 난 없어
i'm using you
나는 당신을 사용하고 있습니다
i always want to
난 항상 그러고 싶어
Be your scapegoat
당신의 희생양이 되세요
and take you to the beach
그리고 당신을 해변으로 데려가세요
Have you met Gao Tianyang?
Gao Tianyang을 만나보셨나요?
I went out in the afternoon
나는 오후에 나갔다.
Mr. Gao
가오 씨
Isn't this appropriate?
이것이 적절하지 않습니까?
Is this impolite?
이건 무례한 일인가요?
I have to keep him safe
나는 그를 안전하게 지켜야 해
we can
우리는 할 수 있다
Let’s talk next time
다음에 얘기하자
his safety
그의 안전
You need to alternate actions
대체 조치를 취해야 합니다.
your terms
귀하의 조건
very difficult for me
나에게는 매우 어렵다
i need more time
시간이 더 필요해
Decide
결정하다
During this period
이 기간 동안
I hope Huang Ziqing is safe
황자칭이 무사하길 바랍니다
sorry
죄송합니다
this is not
이것은 아니다
equality
평등
you don't have much time
시간이 별로 없어
Let's play an old game
옛날 게임을 해보자
Russian wheel
러시안 휠
Do you dare to come?
감히 오시겠어요?
If I say I can't play
내가 놀 수 없다고 말하면
you have to find a way
넌 방법을 찾아야 해
force me
저를 강제로